extramarks.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy | Extramarks

  * Extramarks Education India Pvt. Ltd. (“Extramarks” or the “Company”) is registered at 506, Surya Kiran Building, 19 KG marg, Connaught Place, New Delhi - 110001 and corporate office at D-180, Sector 63, Noida (U.P) – 201301.
  * This Privacy Policy provides you with details about the manner in which your data is collected, stored and used by us. You are advised to read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting Extramarks' website/applications you expressly give us consent to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the policy, please do not use or access Extramarks website, or mobile applications.
  * **Note:** Our Privacy Policy may change at any time without prior notification. To make sure that you are aware of any changes, kindly review the Privacy Policy periodically. This Privacy Policy shall apply uniformly across all Extramarks products, including its website, mobile applications, Tablet and other associated applications, products, websites and services managed by the Company.

#### GENERAL

  * We will not sell, share or rent your personal information to any third party, unless, we have been expressly authorized by you either in writing or electronically to do so. Further, we will not use your email address/mobile number for unsolicited emails and/or SMS. Any emails and/or SMS sent by Extramarks will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products and this Privacy Policy.
  * Periodically, we may reveal general statistical information about Extramarks users, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc. This will not have any identifiable information of any user.
  * Extramarks will occasionally send email notices or contact you to communicate about our services, products and benefits, as they are considered an essential part of the services/products you have chosen.
  * We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

  * Personal Information means and includes all information that can be linked to a specific individual or to identify any individual, such as name, address, mailing address, telephone number, email ID, etc.
  * When you browse through Extramarks, we may collect information regarding the domain and host from which you access the internet, the Internet Protocol [IP] address of the computer/ mobile phone or Internet service provider [ISP] you are using, and anonymous site statistical data.

#### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

  * We use personal information to provide you with services and products you explicitly requested for, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot concerns, help promote safe services, collect money, measure consumer interest in our services, inform you about offers, products, services, updates, customize your experience, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions, etc.
  * We also use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and interests. We may occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, gender, etc.). We use this data to customize your experience at Extramarks. Your data may periodically be transmitted to external service providers to help us improve the application, products and our services. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy.

#### COOKIES

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Extramarks uses cookies and tracking technology depending on the features offered. No personal information will be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you have previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. This is applicable only for website.

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITE

Our site provides links to other third party websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites, and you are solely responsible for visiting such third party websites.

#### SECURITY

Extramarks has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

#### DURATION OF RETENTION OF DATE

Extramarks shall retain user data during the term an account is active and for at least three years thereafter. The Company may alter this practice according to legal and business requirements.

#### CONSENT

By using Extramarks and/or by registration on Extramarks, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on Extramarks in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this Privacy Policy.

#### CONTACT US

Should you have any doubt relating to this Privacy Policy, you may get in touch with us at [customersupport@extramarks.com](mailto:customersupport@extramarks.com)

#### DISPUTE RESOLUTION

In case of any dispute, the same shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts situated at Delhi.

### Free Expert Advise

Inviting all students to avail a **10 minutes FREE counseling session** to discuss concerns related to studies, exam phobia, stream selections, time management, coping with stress, exam preparation etc.

Call us today at Toll Free Number: 1800-102-5301 and get your questions answered!
